We're here in the middle of butt-fuck
nowhere in the desert.
This is where the cartel come to hide dead
bodies.
As long as everyone does their jobs today,
there shall be no more dead bodies added
to that list.
Do I have to worry?
No, more so Chris.
Okay.
Sometimes pretending that I like him
is exhausting.
[laughs]
This is uncomfortable on my head. This
is uncomfortable on my head.
Pretending that we get on is exhausting.
Working with him is exhausting.
So we're just about to start filming,
but no, Chris wants a waffle from Denny's,
so
we'll all wait.
Crocs in the desert were a bad choice,
mate.
White socks, Crocs in the desert,
bad choice. No one shows me shit.
No one shows me anything. I just turn up.
[knocks]
Yes?
If I give you this camera,
can you take some pictures of your day
and give it back
to me at the end?
All right. Go away.
You want to shoot today?
Yeah.
If I give you this camera,
can you take some pictures
and give it back to me at the
end?
Hold up a sec.
[laughs]
[gentle music]
I don't think there's any health
and safety here.
So far, I've been playing with dry ice.
I've been standing on an RV.
My life has well and truly been
endangered.
So the things you do for promotional
content. Whoa!
Woo!
Yes. Yes, mate.
Oh, we have to use sounds on these.
Let him cook, bro.
Let him cook.
Let him cook. And then just like
[mimics explosion] . Take a bit of
change out of my pockets for this scene.
Jackline, come here. I've got a strategy.
So-
All right
... every can of Nutonic... Do you smell?
I don't know what that was.
Just checked that.
Every can of Nutonic I have,
I feel better.
So my strategy is to continue consuming
them until I start to feel worse, because
it's going to flatten out at some point,
and I'm going to keep going, accrue the
marginal gains at the top.
Then as soon as it just begins to peter
off, then I'm
going to [clicks tongue] So I'm three cans
deep. We'll see where I get to.
Maybe don't put that in the edit.
Have you got an arse tattoo?
Yeah.
What's it say?
[laughs]
Your name.
Rugby.
No, just I got drunk.
Thought it'd be funny. Still is.
And then I spent the next few years going
up to girls, and I'd meet girls at the
bar, and I'd be like,
"What's your name?" They'd be like,
"Chiante." I'd be like,
"Oh my God,
you won't believe this." They go,
"Why?" "I've got your name tattooed
on my arse." "No, you don't."
And I'd be like, "I'll show you.
I bet you a shot of tequila." So I get
random girls with really random names,
mostly Black, to [laughs] buy me drinks.
Genius, innit?
[laughs]
I might have to do a mangina for health
and safety.
Thank you.
Just come in front of him.
[laughs]
Stand in front of him.
Just stand in front of him.
[laughs]
And that's a wrap. Four days in LA,
all promotion for the new drink.
That's how you market a business.
That's how you bring it to market.
It's what we do behind the scenes.
I hope you guys enjoy it.
I'll put a link in the description
where you can please try some out
yourself.